Guide to the Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015.
Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015
- Series VII. Education and Outreach, 1980-2004
  - National Coming Out Day (NCOD)
    - National Coming Out Day press releases, Jason Serinus, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 0)
    - HRC--National Coming Out Project-Drafts: "A History of NCOD", 2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - National Coming Out Project--Kit, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - National Coming Out Project-Draft "Coming Out Resource Guide", Draft Spanish Language Translation, Aug 2001 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - National Coming Out Project-Info Packet, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - HRC Spokesperson NCOD Project, Betty DeGeneres, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - NCOP-Esera Tuaolo, 2002-2003 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Being Out Rocks, promotion and press coverage, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Being Out Rocks, Correspondence, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - NCOP, various, 2002-03 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - "Being Out Rocks" Press Kit, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Coming Out Day - Sponsor Orgs list, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - National Coming Out Day poster (Box 127, Folder 39)
- Series VIII. Research
  Records from the predecessor organization, Right to Privacy Foundation, and HRC's nonprofit, tax-exempt 501(c)(3) units devoted to research and analysis: the Human Rights and Health Fund, The Triangle Institute (TTI), and the HRC Foundation.
  - Right to Privacy Foundation (RPF), 1981-1989
    Records of the Right to Privacy Foundation, founded by Steve Endean, which researched anti-discrimination in employment, the federal Gay Civil Rights Bill, and HIV/AIDS discrimination. Consists mostly of administrative records. Also includes files on civil rights and direct marketing materials showing efforts at raising money to support their HIV and AIDS related lobbying work.
    - RPF- Articles of Incorporation-certificate, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - RPF- Mailings: re: Civil Rights, 1979-80 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - RPF- Materials re: Civil Rights Amendment Acts, 1980-83 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - RPF- Financial Status Records and Financial Statements, 1981-84 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - RPF- Taxes - Misc., 1981-84 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - RPF- Post Office Box & Postage, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - RPF- Internal Revenue Service, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - RPF- Teresa Sullivan Associates-Bills, 1982-83 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - RPF- Draft Bylaws, Proposed Budget, 1982-95 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - RPF- Taxes-Forms Filed, 1982-1984 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - RPF- Direct Mail Fundraising Budget & Letter, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - RPF-Federal Gay Civil Rights Legislation: Bills, Status, RPF memo, 1983-84 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - RPF-Financial Statements and Reports, Correspondence with IRS, 1984-86 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - RPF-Right to Privacy Grant Proposal to Chicago Resource Ctr., 1985 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - RPF- AIDS- Insurance anti-discrimination laws, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - RPF- Executive Board Correspondence, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - RPF- Federal Tax Form 942, 1987-88 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - RPF- Voter Registration -Interfaith Action for Interfaith Justice, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Direct Mail prospecting- T. Sullivan Assoc., 9/1982- Oct. 1983 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Right to Privacy Form Letters, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Board Update- from R. Davis- Education & Research Director, Dec 1982 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Right to Privacy Foundation Board of Directors Meeting, April 30 1983 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - RPF/GRNL Fundraiser- Hispanic G/L Comm. in VA, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Grant Proposal- Stroh Brewery, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Budget, expenditures, 1982-84 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Tony Silvestre's Archival donations, June 2010 (Box 127, Folder 40)
    - Creation and Establishment, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 41)
    - Rick Davis: Education and Research Director (Box 127, Folder 42)
    - Board Members (Box 127, Folder 43)
    - Board meeting minutes, January 23, 1986 (Box 127, Folder 44)
    - Appeal Mailing, June 10, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 45)
    - Community/Constituency Service and Education (Box 127, Folder 46)
    - Notes (Box 127, Folder 47)
  - Human Rights and Health Fund (HRHF) Inherited Files, 1977-1985
    Past polls and correspondence collected and used by the Human Rights and Health Fund and its successors.
    - Polls - G/L/B/T Issues (various pollsters), 1977, 1981, 1982, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Polls - NBC News/AP, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - GNRL/NGLTF Political Study Report, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights Amendments Acts, 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Various Polls-results, news stories, 1981-85 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Various Polls, Surveys-results, news stories, 1983-85 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Presidential Surveys (NGTF/GRNL/HRCF), 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Attitudes towards Homosexuality-student papers, Cornell Univ., 1985 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Lesbian & Gay Democrats, Elected Officials, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Report by Steven Endean, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - State Lobbying literature (MGPC, MOHR), 1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Voter Research Foundation, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence with D. Goodstein, 1982-1983 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Human Rights and Health Fund (HRHF), 1986-February 1988
    Created in 1986, the Human Rights and Health Fund and its successors, the Triangle Institute and then the HRC Foundation, have been nonprofit, tax-exempt 501(c)(3) organizations that support the work of HRC through research, educational efforts, and outreach.
    Included under the Human Rights and Health Fund are administrative files and issue files on gay politics, key races, polling data, minority AIDS outreach, and MEDPAC clippings. Some project files were passed along to The Triangle Institute and are merged with those files.
    - HRHF Administration
      The administrative files include R. Brady's chronological correspondence files, budgets and financial reports, articles of incorporation and bylaws, the application for 501(c) 3 status, and notes from Board of Directors meetings.
      - Misc. Memos, Correspondence, etc., 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - HRHF/TTI Management Reports, Sept. 1982-July 1988, 1982-1988 (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - Legal Counsel- Establishing (501c3), 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 36)
      - R. Brady Chronology File, Oct - Dec 1987 (Box 40, Folder 37)
      - R. Brady Chronology File, Jan - Apr 1988 (Box 40, Folder 38)
      - R. Brady Chronology File, May-June 1988 (Box 40, Folder 39)
      - R. Brady Chronology File, Jul.-Sept. 1988 (Box 40, Folder 40)
      - Articles of Incorporation & Bylaws, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 41)
      - Tax Bequest Information (general), 1986 (Box 40, Folder 42)
      - Cost Allocation Agreement, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 43)
      - HRHF Non-Profit Corporation Application, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 44)
      - Financial Statement Report, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - HRHF Application for 501(c) 3 Status, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Org. Meeting, Oct. 1986 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Financial Statements (March-Nov.), 1987 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - 501(c) 3 issues- Board of Directors Meeting, April 1987 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Summary Financials, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - 1988 Annual Budget, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Financial Reports 1987-88, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Legal Requirements for 501c3/REB, 1986-88 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - IRS Tax-Exemption Materials, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Board of Directors Meeting May 1987 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting Oct. 1987 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Board of Directors Materials and Minutes, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Board of Directors Meeting Nov. 1987 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Board of Directors Meeting Dec. 1987 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Board of Directors Correspondence / Resignation Letters, 1987-88 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - HRHF Board Meetings, 1987,1988 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Board of Directors Meeting Jan. 1988 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Board of Directors Meeting Feb. 1988 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Board of Directors Meeting March 1988 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Board of Directors Meeting April 1988 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Board of Directors Meeting May 1988 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Board of Directors Meeting June 1988 (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - Board of Directors Meeting July 1988 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - Board of Directors Meeting Sept. 1988 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - HRHF Issues
      - c3 Project: Key Political Races, 1986-87 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Minority AIDS Outreach (reports, notes, newsletter), 1986-88 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Polling Data (Results, Reports, PR), 1986-88 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Mertz-Gilmore Foundation - HRHF Correspondence, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Reports on Politics of AIDS, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Congressional Member / Committee Lists - 99th & 100th Congresses, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Foundation Listing - Possible Grantors, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Civic Service Inc. / Van Dyk & Assoc., 1987 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - MEDPAC Clipping Package, Sept. 1987 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - MEDPAC Clipping Service of AIDS Medical Developments, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Human Rights and Health Fund News Clippings, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Gay/Lesbian elected officials, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - The Politics of AIDS: Risk and Empathy on the Epidemiological Frontier (Nov. 3, 1987) (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - United Way - Combined Federal Campaign D.C., 1987-88 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - HRHF Case Statements, 1987-88 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Gay-Lesbian Activists/Outlets, 1987-88 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - Advisory Committee-Ideas & Examples, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Research viability study materials, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Survey '88: National Visibility Campaign, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - The Analysis Group, Stanley B. Greenberg (Democratic poll taker)--"The Politics of AIDS" and other issues, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - The Triangle Institute (TTI), Mar. 1988-1995
    In March 1988, HRHF changed its name to The Triangle Institute (TTI) and was active under this name until 1995. Its programs included the Electoral Research Project (ERP), the MEDPAC project focused on disseminating reliable information related to the AIDS crisis, and after 1993, the National Coming Out Day Project (NCOD). Documented here are TTI's fund raising through grant applications and direct marketing and HRHF/TTI Board meeting packets and some of its project files. The files on the Electoral Research Project and on AIDS projects include earlier work done by HRHF. The current documentation is limited to activities from 1986 to 1988.
    NCOD files are in a separate subseries. Other important TTI documents can be found in the Education Department's 20th Year History Project files (series VII).
    - ERP information packet - The Triangle Institute, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Campaign professional: Focus group transcripts, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Connecticut and Missouri Focus Groups: transcripts, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Managing the Gay Rights Endorsement, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Board member packet - From The Analysis Group re: ERP, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Electoral Research Project (ERP) Content Pieces, 1986-88 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Memos and notes re: Electoral Research Project (ERP), 1988 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - ERP - survey instrument, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - ERP correspondence w/Analysis Group, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - ERP correspondence w/Analysis Group, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - League of Gay and Lesbian Voters - Info Packet, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - AIDS: A Status Report on Foundation Funding The Foundation Center - TTI annotated copy, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Notes re: requests for grant funding applications, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - CDC Assistance Grant Proposal: AIDS information and education programs, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - AmFAR: American Foundation for AIDS Research - grants, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation: AIDS Prevention and Service Projects - grants, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Triangle Institute-Formation, 1987-88 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Electoral Research Project - misc. admin, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - New World Foundation - Grants (1988) (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - New World Foundation - Grants, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Funding Exchange Proposal, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - Gay Politics-Affiliated Organizations (APA, NASW, APA, et al.), 1988 (Box 40, Folder 50)
    - March on Washington DC-Press list, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 51)
    - TTI - Literature Search, Bibliography G/L/B/T, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 52)
    - TTI - Logo/Design working docs, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 53)
    - TTI - Academic Networks G/L/B/T, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 54)
    - TTI - Triangle Institute "Homosexual Demographic" Survey materials, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 55)
    - J. Roderick Foundation information, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 56)
    - TTI - National March on Washington for Lesbian & Gay Rights, Proposal, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 57)
    - TTI - Playboy Foundation - Grant, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 58)
    - Astraea Foundation, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 59)
    - TTI - The Forum Institute, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 60)
    - Chicago Resource Center - Grants, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 61)
    - TTI - The Advocate - Letter to the Editor - Responses, Spring 1988 (Box 40, Folder 62)
    - W.R. Hearst Foundation - Grants, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 63)
    - German Marshall Fund - Grants, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 64)
    - The Next Step / AIDSWalk - Proposal, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 65)
    - Brother Help Thyself - Proposal, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 66)
    - TTI - Triangle Institute: News Clippings, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 67)
    - TTI - "Counter Hate Count Crimes" Hate Crimes Statistics Act stickers (Box 40, Folder 68)
    - TTI - Research: Domestic Partners (Box 40, Folder 69)
    - TTI - Donor Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Institutional Donors/Prospects for the Electoral Research Project, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Individual Donors/Prospects, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - HRC Foundation
    In 1995, TTI became the Human Rights Campaign Foundation. Programs funded in part or in full through the Human Rights Campaign Foundation include: the Historically Black Colleges and Universities Outreach Program, Family Project, Workplace Project, National Coming Out Project, Religion and Faith Program, and the HRC Research Institute.
    Workplace and WorkNet project files and some National Coming Out Day files are found under the Communication and Education series. Foundation bylaws and two folders with articles about HRC Foundation events and staff can be found in the Education Department's 20th Year History Project files (series VII). No additional records from the HRC Foundation have been transferred to the archives yet.
  - AIDS Research, 1981-1998
    The collected files related to AIDS research generated and collected by HRC's 501c units, including administrative files and correspondence about the AIDS Federal Policy Act and other issues documenting the work of this unit, MEDPAC packets (press clippings related to HIV and AIDS issues), reports issued by other agencies, subject files, and files related to the publication Guide to Public Health: Principles to Protect HIV-related Confidentiality and Prevent Discrimination, Washington, DC: Association of State and Territorial Health Officers, 1988. Files on AIDS are also found throughout the collection.
    - Administration
      - HRCF-Correspondence-AIDS Federal Policy Act (HR3071 and S. 1575), 1987 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - HRCF - Wexler/Reynolds AIDS Research Mgmt, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Testimony about Ampligen trial at MHC in NYC, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - NORA (National Organizations Responding to AIDS), 1988-89 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Department of Labor, Health, and Human Services, and Education, and Related Agencies Appropriation Bill, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - MEDPAC
      - HRCF --MEDPAC (AIDS related articles, info), June 29, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - HRCF --MEDPAC (AIDS related articles, info), Aug 6, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - HRCF --MEDPAC Jan 29, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - HRCF--MEDPAC March 22, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Reports
      - America Responds to AIDS: Final Report "Listening and the American Response", 1987 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - "Nontraditional Approaches to the Medical Malpractice Crisis": AHA Office of Legal and Regulatory Affairs, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Congressional Clearinghouse on the Future, information packet, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Community-Based Care for Persons with AIDS. Aetna Insurance Group, Public Policy Issues Group., Dec. 1987 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - "AIDS Drugs: Where are They?" by the Committee on Government Operations, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Milbank Quarterly: "HIV and Childbearing", 1990 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files
      - U.S. Patent & Technology Transfer--Codes, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Symposium 1987: Labor and Employment Issues Raised by AIDS and HIV Infection: District of Columbia Bar, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - AIDS Drugs Info-Petition to HHS/Testimony by Adler, NIH, 1986, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - AIDS drugs and FDA regulation materials, 1987-89 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - AIDS and People of Color: Subject File, 1987-88 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - AIDS drugs info., clippings, Press Releases, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - AIDS Drugs: News clippings, press releases, fact sheets, 1988-90 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - HRCF State and Local Legislation- AIDS, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - HRCF Manhattan Project on AIDS- drafts, ideas, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - AIDS & People of Color, 1986-87 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - AIDS & Prisons- Literature, clippings, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - AIDS- Jewish Response, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - News Clippings [AIDS], 1985-86 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - AIDS: Peptide T- scientific literature, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - AIDS- Public Opinion Polls, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Safe Sex Guidelines for Gay Men, 1986? (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Sweeny Speech- SEIU- Safe working practices re: blood borne diseases, 1986? (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - AIDS in school- articles, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - AIDS- medical Literature, 1980s (Box 41, Folder 34)
      - AIDS Testing- News articles, public opinion, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 35)
      - Violence & Discrimination against G/L People in Philadelphia, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 36)
      - AIDS Commission- US Presidential Comm. on HIV, 1987-88 (Box 41, Folder 37)
      - AIDS Commission- Presidential Comm. on HIV Epidemic Report, Mar 1988 (Box 41, Folder 38)
      - AIDS Discrimination- Section 504 of Rehabilitation Act of 1973, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 39)
      - AIDS Discrimination Section 504, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 40)
      - "Reports on AIDS published in The Morbidity & Mortality Weekly Report", June 1981- 1986 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Guide to Public Health Practice: Principles to Protect HIV-Related Confidentiality and Prevent Discrimination
      - ASTHO/Health officers (Box 41, Folder 42)
      - Health Care Workers & New OSHA/NIOSH Advisory (Box 41, Folder 43)
      - AIDS and Prisons (Box 41, Folder 44)
      - Immigrants/Tourists (Box 41, Folder 45)
      - Marital Screening/Dole remarks (Box 41, Folder 46)
      - The Accuracy of AIDS Testing (Box 41, Folder 47)
      - The Case Against Compulsory Testing (Box 41, Folder 48)
      - CDC Testing Guidelines (Box 41, Folder 49)
      - Impact Overview & A Legal Perspective (Box 41, Folder 50)
      - Surgeon General's Report & Section Three: Rebuttal Info (Box 41, Folder 51)
      - Inst. Of Med. Pub. Health Rec. (Box 41, Folder 52)
      - Section Two: AIDS 101 & The Science of AIDS (Box 41, Folder 53)
      - Care Needs/Cost (Box 41, Folder 54)
      - Paid Advertising Awareness & The Need for Education & Expediting Research & Staff/Space Needs at NIH & International Efforts (Box 41, Folder 55)
      - Section One: S. 101 & Why an Authorizing Bill? & American Nurses Association & Discrimination & Airline Security 504 (Box 41, Folder 56)
      - American Medical Association & Confidentiality (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - National Coming Out Day (NCOD) Files, 1987-
    This subseries contains the inherited files of the original organization that started National Coming Out day in 1987 and the files after 1993, when the Human Rights Campaign Fund took it over. The NCOD merger documents can be found in the Education Department's 20th Year History Project files (series VII).
    - Inherited files, NCOD organization, 1988-1993
      - Administrative
        - NCOD-The Big Book-Folder 1, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - NCOD-The Big Book-Folder 2, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 2)
        - NCOD-The Big Book-Folder 3, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - NCOD-The Big Book-Folder 4, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - NCOD-The Big Book-Folder 5, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 5)
        - NCOD-The Big Book-Folder 6, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - NCOD-The Big Book-Folder 7, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 7)
        - NCOD-The Big Book-Folder 8, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - NCOD- Administrative Misc., 1992 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Subject Files
        - NCOD- Ads placed by NCOD, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 10)
        - NCOD- AIDS, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11)
        - NCOD- Anti-Gay literature and reports, 1985, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 12)
        - NCOD- Awards Given, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 13)
        - NCOD- Catalogs selling NCOD merchandise, 1991-92 (Box 50, Folder 14)
        - NCOD- Conferences where NCOD exhibited, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 15)
        - NCOD- Coordinators, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 16)
        - NCOD- Correspondence, 1991-93 (Box 50, Folder 17)
        - NCOD- Direct Mail Vendors, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 18)
        - NCOD- Films and Videos, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 19)
        - NCOD- Gay Rights Bills (CO), 1991 (Box 50, Folder 20)
        - NCOD- Lesbian Resources, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 21)
        - NCOD- Lists (Box 50, Folder 22)
        - NCOD- Non-discriminatory Policies, 1987, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 23)
        - NCOD- Scout Letters, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 24)
        - NCOD- Studies and Surveys, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 25)
        - NCOD- Subject & Organization Files A-C, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 26)
        - NCOD- Subject & Organization Files D (Box 50, Folder 27)
        - NCOD- Subject & Organization Files E-F, 1990-92 (Box 50, Folder 28)
        - NCOD- Subject & Organization Files G, 1990-94 (Box 50, Folder 29)
        - NCOD- Subject & Organization Files H-M, 1984, 1990-92 (Box 50, Folder 30)
        - NCOD- Subject & Organization Files N, 1990-92 (Box 50, Folder 31)
        - NCOD- Subject & Organization Files O, 1990-92 (Box 50, Folder 32)
        - NCOD- Subject & Organization Files P, 1984-1992 (Box 50, Folder 33)
        - NCOD- Subject & Organization Files S-V (Box 50, Folder 34)
        - NCOD-Logos (Box 50, Folder 35)
        - NCOD- Computer Docs (Box 50, Folder 36)
        - NCOD- LA Committee (Box 50, Folder 37)
        - NCOD-PSA, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 38)
        - NCOD- United We Stand, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 39)
        - NCOD- Staff Meetings, 1990-92 (Box 50, Folder 40)
        - NCOD Coming Out Ad campaign 1990 (photographs, corresp.) (Box 50, Folder 41)
        - NCOD Publicity, awards, etc., 1989 (Box 50, Folder 42)
        - NCOD- National Coming Out Day Kit & Buttons, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 43)